<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integration Overview on PaySuper</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integration Overview on PaySuper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>PaySuper payment solution can be either used in combination with other Protocol One components, or integrated into any third-party storefront or web page that must accept payments.
Pay One is an SaaS solution operated by Protocol One. A similar payment solution can be deployed on your own servers or in the cloud using the Pay One open source code.
To get started  You need to register on the Pay One website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PaySuper Integration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/integration/</guid>
      <description>In the case of basic payment acceptance, the integration process takes just a few minutes.
Steps of the integration process:
PaySuper website signup To begin, we need only basic information about your company:
 name jurisdiction, website address.  You can get started immediately and use PaySuper in test mode.
API access keys will be generated automatically and can be changed later.
Along with the next steps, you’ll need to go through the KYC procedure and sign the contract with an e-signature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project and Products</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/project-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/project-products/</guid>
      <description>The project-level management approach It allows you to independently configure PaySuper for use in various contexts:
 different games sites with different payment logic specialized solutions for a particular region or a specific cohort of users.  Any information about payments in this configuration can be reflected in the reports and analytics both cumulatively and separately.
Modes of operation in project Simple checkout In this mode, you transfer the payment sum for each specific transaction to Pay One.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Account</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/personal-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/personal-account/</guid>
      <description> An account with Pay One is the main point of interaction with Pay One for all your employees.
The account contains tools for:  Account settings Project settings, including the launch of integration tests and product management Webhook configuration Transaction search, including full-text search for all attributes Returns management Dispute management Viewing reports and statistics Viewing and managing payouts Managing the rights of account users  The account supports:  Two-factor user authentication Real-time data updates Exporting all reports in CSV and XLSX formats  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reports Dashboard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/reports/</guid>
      <description>Examples of reports available on the dashboard and in the Reports section:
 Recent transactions. Revenue dynamics that can be broken down by project or product, with different levels of detail (day, week, month, year). Country statistics in the form of a table or heat map, where you can choose a period, projects and products. Returns report. Payouts report and a transactional report on a specific payout. Payment methods report, where you can choose a period, projects and products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External Reports</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/external-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/getting-started/external-reports/</guid>
      <description>When internal reports are not enough, you can connect an external analytics tool (for example, tableau or slemma) or your own data visualization tool.
You can access the data or, using the API, upload data to your storage. We adhere to the OLAP cube structure.
Dimensions:
 Project Product Geography Payment currency Payment method Payment date Return date User agent  Measures:
 The sum in payment currency The sum in payout currency Number of transactions  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>