<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Payments Overview on PaySuper</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/payments/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Payments Overview on PaySuper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepting a Payment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payments/accepting-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payments/accepting-payment/</guid>
      <description>Steps of the accepting a payment process:
Interaction with the payment interface  The user begins their interaction with the payment form by clicking on an interface element on the website. The form is displayed in accordance with regional features and project settings. The form responds to user actions with minimal user interface delays. In the interface, the user selects a payment method (when possible), enters plastic card information or credentials for another means of payment, passes KYC elements if necessary or fills in data required for product delivery (for example, an email or instant messenger contact to receive the key).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-form/</guid>
      <description>Payment forms are optimized for display on a wide range of mobile devices (tablets and smartphones). The display logic takes into account the device-specific touch controls and the use of an on-screen keyboard.
You can customize the form yourself, setting up both general properties and regional features. Pay One offers a variety of pre-made templates. The solution provides personalized recommendations for using templates based on user conversions in stores similar to yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment Methods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-methods/</guid>
      <description>At this point we can process:
 Plactic cards, with or without 3D-Secure China Union Pay Neteller A number of cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum Qiwi Alipay WeChat Webmoney Bank transfers Payment methods of Latin America Payment methods of South Asia Payment methods of Africa  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Payment Processing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/payments/payment-processing/</guid>
      <description>Simple HTML Form This method allows you to create an invoice by transferring a simple HTML form to the side of the payment system and is the easiest way to invoice the customer for payment. System requests for checking order data and notifications about successful payment of an order are received routinely in accordance with the system protocol.
Basic algorithm of payment processing:
 The buyer initiates a transaction by pressing &amp;ldquo;Buy&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>